wand.com 2000-12-07

# Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement for wand.com and other  
WAND® Custom Directory Sites**

WAND, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for wand.com and all other applicable WAND® Directory Network Partner sites. 

Your IP address is used to help identify log your session information. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. WAND, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**Security**   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control and will make every effort to maintain the security and privacy of that information. 

**Supplementation Information**   
This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our Directory Network Partners and us. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

    1\. You can send email to [strick@wand.com](mailto:strick@wand.com)
    2\. You can call the following telephone number: 303-623-1200 x240 

**Correct/Update**   
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

    1\. email [jsweeney@wand.com](mailto:jsweeney@wand.com)
    3\. call the following telephone number: 303-623-1200 x225 

**Contacting the Web Site**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

    Jim Dwyer 
    WAND, Inc. 
    1514 Curtis St. 
    Denver, CO 80202 
Search WAND® | About WAND® | New Listings | WAND® Global News | Tradeshow Listings   
Country Information | WAND® Services | Global Contacts | Contact WAND® | Other Languages | HOME  Contact WAND®

Disclaimer and Legal Notice   
Privacy Statement
